Guide to the William Rainey Harper Papers 1872-1938
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Correspondence, September 24, - October 18, 1895, Adams, Pres. Blatchford, E.W. Briggs, C.C. Carroll, Rev. B.H. Chase, Mr. Faunce, W.H.P. Fellows, Prof. Geo. E. Frost, Charles Hamilton Goodman and Dickerson, Co. Haskell, C.E. Head, Franklin H. James, Prof. E.J. Kent, Prof. Chas. F. Kohlsaat, H.H. Manning, Rev. R.E. Smith, George Adam Stuart, Lewis Watt, Alex (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, October 19 - November 15, 1895, Baer, John Willis Blanchard, Charles A. Bradley, Charles, F. Bulkley, Miss Butler, Nicholas Murray Faunce, W.H.P. Hovey, Prof. Geo. R. Hoyt, John W. James, E.J. Nightingale, Mr. Sherrill, A.F. Towne, Mr. E.C. Van Osdel, Mr. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, November 18, - December 29, 1895, Baer, John Willis Broholm, Aug. Bruce, Prof. Coulter, Pres. J.M. Cressey, Charles H. Edwards, Dr. Arthur T. Fish, Frederick S. Fisher, Walter l. (University Club) Funk, I.K. (of Funk and Wagnalls) Hall, T. Proctor Ingals, Dr. E. Fletcher Jones, Miss Laura A. Kohlsaat, H.H. See, T.J.J Shepardson Slocum, Pres. A. Gaylord Soares, Theo. D. Stuart, Lewis (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, January 6, - January 31, 1896, Burton, E. D. Butler, Pres. Nathaniel Capps, Mr. Chandler, Prof. Dewey, Prof. John Henderson, Dr. C.R. Hitchcock, Albert W. Kellogg, Dr. Lincoln, Robert T. Lovett, Mr. Patten, Arthur B. Price, Prof. Sanders, Frank K. Small, Prof. Smith, George Adam Strong, Josiah Thurber, Mr. Van Eyck, C. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, January 31 - February 26, 1896, Aked, Charles F. Battes, Geo. Baur, Prof. George Beiler, S.L. Boughton, Prof. Willis Briggs, C.A. Butterick, Wallace Cherry, B. A. Dulles, Rev. J.H. Gould, Prof. E.L.K. Henderson, Prof. James, Prof. Edmund J. Johnson, Harvey Jordan, Mr. Kent, Charles F. Laughlin, Prof. McCartney, W.P. Michelson Moore, E.H. Small, Prof. Wolkonsky, Prince Sergi (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, March 3, - March 25, 1896, Aked, C.F. Bartlett, Daniel C. Bliss, F.L. Brown, Prof. Crippen, Mrs. Abbie Cutting Dixson, Mrs. Dudley, Oscar L. Jones, Laura A. Kent, Prof. C.F. Lewis, Mr. Edwin H. Lovett Rowlands, A.J. See, T.J.J. Stetson, H.L. Walker, Mr. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, March 30, - April 28, 1896, Aked, Charles F. Barrows, Dr. Blakelee, T.M. Brown, Charles Rufus Chase, C.E. Dahl, Mr. Claus Flood, Ned Arden Gordon, Dr. John Hale, W.G. Hastings, Rev. Frederick Hatcher, W.E. Henderson, Dr. McLeish Nightingale Ryerson Stetson, Pres. Thornton, Charles S. Weaver, L.R. Wolkonsky, Prince Serge (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, April 30, - May 20, 1896, Andrews, Pres. E. Benjamin Bitting, W.C. Buttrick, Wallace Cipriani, Lisi Curtis, J.B. Easley, R.H. Estabrook, Henry D. Fortune, G. W. France, Miss Kohlsaat, H.H. Krause, Max Lamson, L.J. Laughlin, Prof. Manny, F. A. Mathews, Shailer Parsons, Rev. F.W. Peck, Ferd. W. Smith, George A. Ward, William C. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, May 20, - May 30, 1896, Aldrich J. Frank Breasted, Mr. Burrows, S.S. Child, Mr. Culver, Helen Dunn, Arthur W. Dye, Gordon Fortune, Rev. Geo. M. Freeman, Henry V. Gessler, Rev. Theo. A.K. Gurney, Mr. Judson Meier, Rev. J. Mitchell, S.C. Pond, J.B. Squires, Mr. Willcox, Miss M.A. Williams, Mr. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, June 1, - June 23, 1896, Bruner, Mr. Buzzell, E.K. Dunn, John Fay, C.N. Freeman, Miss Gardner, Henry A. Gurney, Mr. Hale, Mr. Harper, R.F. Haskell, Mrs. Henderson, Prof. Nightingale, Supt. Pond, James B. Rairden, N.B. Small, Albion State, Prof. Bernhard Swift, Mayor Triggs, Mr. Walker, Prof. Wallace, Prof. James Warner, Charles Dudley Williams, Wardner Zeublin, J.E. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, June 23 - June 29, 1896 and Addenda, Buttrick, Wallace Ingals, Dr. E. Fletcher McLeigh, Mrs. Parker, Francis W. Patten, Arthur B. Seaman, Allen B. Smith, George Adam Whitman (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, July 6 -- July 31, 1896, Barrows, Dr. John Henry Bridgman, Supt. I.M. Caldwell, Mr. Capps Carman, Principal Geo. N. Cheney, J.V. Dixson, Mrs. Harper, R.F. Haskell, Mrs. Caroline Hubbard, Pres. Gardiner G. Johnson, Dean Franklin Laughlin, Prof. Lyon, Prof. D.G. Pike, J. Reynolds, James B. Robinson, Mrs. Harriet P. Rundell, E.R. Squires, Mr. Strong, Augustus H. Thurber, Mr. Von Holst, Prof. Whitman, G.O. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, July 31 -- August 25, 1896, Bruce, Hon. James Burnham, Prof. Sylvester Cadman, James P. Carpenter, Prof. J.E. Chase, Mr. Cheney, J.V. Cobb, Miss Culver, Miss Curtis, A.B. Donaldson, Mr. Harding, Mrs. Susan Kohlsaat, Judge C.C. Laughlin Mallory, H.F. Prinzing, Miss Louise Ryan, Eugene Salisbury, Mr. Smith, Emily J. Smith, George Adam Spalding, Bishop White, Rev. James (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, August 26, -- September 21, 1896, Aberdeen, Countess of Anderson, Kate Bancroft, Prof. Frederic Bulkley, Miss Burgess, I.B. Burkhalter, Capt. James L. Butler, Pres. N. Carroll, B. H. Dixson, Mrs. Donnelley, Mr. Fletcher, Dr. C.O. Green, Andrew H. Gregory, Prof. Casper Rene Harper, Robert F. Henderson, C.R. Hodder and Stoughton Jackson, Rev. John L. Leiser, Joseph Lovett, R.M. Luzac and Co. Manning, Rev. R.E. McKee, W.P. Millikan, R.A. Seay, Prof. A.G. Tarbell, Prof. Tomlins, W.L. Walker, Mr. Waterman, Richard (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, September 22 -- October 16, 1896, Armour, Geo. Allison Austin, R.H. Brown, Prof. Francis Bryce, Hon. James Bulkley, Miss Burton Culver, Miss Helen Fay, C.N. Hoge, Rev. Peyton H. Homewood Club, Steward of Jordon, Mr. Lovett, R.M. Miller, Prof. Nathan, Adolph Pres. Northrup, Rev. Stephen Potter, E.A. Ruth, Mrs. L.C. Tarbell, Prof. Watson, Rev. John Williams, Wardner (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, October 17, - November 7, 1896, Blatchford, E.W. Butler, Chauncey Dewey, Prof. John Fallows, Bishop Fisk, Franklin P. Hirsch, Dr. Judson Mannion, J.F. McClintock, Prof. Morgan, T.S. Moulton, Mr. Peck, Geo. R. Sanday, Prof. W. Schobinger, John J. Small Smith, George Adam Stetson, Pres. Terry, B.S. Van Benthuysen, Mr. Von Holst, Prof. Williams, Wardner (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, November 9 - December 3, 1896, Angell, Pres. Bell, Lillian Blatchford, E.W. Bruce, Prof. Civic Federation, Sec. of Colwell, Prof. R.S. Estabrook, H.D. Foster, Prof. Heath, D.C. James, Prof. Leonard, Gardner C. McCormick, Cyrus H. McPherson, Rev. S.J. Miller, Lewis Miller, Miss Mary Newcomb, Prof. Simon Rees, Louise Stone, Rev. E.A. Talbot, Miss Van Dyke, Henry Wilcox, C.R. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, December 7 - December 29, 1896, Adams, J.Q. (missing) Blake, E. Wilson Chamberlin, T.C. Estabrook, H. D. Ford, Lyman H. Gessler, Sec. Theo. A.K. Hale, Prof. W.G. Halett, H.A. Herrick, Elizabeth Kellly, Rev. A.C. Lewis, Prof. E.H. Manny, Mr. McClintock McKee, W.P. Miller, Prof. E.H. Lewis Rowley, Rev. Francis H. Seymour, Prof. T.D. Smith, Mrs. Mary L.G. Van Inwagen, L.J. Wallace, Miss Watson, Bessie (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, January 4 - February 5, 1896, Aberdeen, Countess of Adams, C.K. Adams, Pres. C.K. Angell Barnard, E.E. Butler, Pres. Nathaniel Buttrick, Wallace Dornard, W.H. Gooch, Hiram A. Gordon, Rev. George A. Hannaford, W.H. Heagle, David Kohlsaat, H.H. Medill, Joseph Princeton University, Trustees of Ryerson Sanders, F.K. See, T.J.J. Vedder, Mrs. H.R. Vincent Walker, Geo. C. Winslow, Dr. William C. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, February 5 - February 20, 1896, Atkins, Mrs. E.C. Brown, Charles Rufus Bulkley, Miss Butler, Pres. (of Colby) Dixson, Mrs. Faunce, W.H.P. Gilbert, Frank Goodspeed Hill, David J. Lovett McClintock Northrup, Dr. Rust, Mr. Ryerson Shorey Stuart, Lewis Talcott, William A. Walters, Prof. John D. Ward, Dr. William Hayes Zeublin, Prof. Zimmerman, Mr. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, February 22 - March 9, 1896, Bagley, H.E. Beeson, Charles H. Bruner, Mr. Burgess, Prof. Burton Butler, Pres. Crane, Alice Emerson, Edward Faunce, W.H.P. Finley, Pres. John Hale Kohlsaat, H.H. Laing, A. Lee, S.H. Manatt, J. Irving McKee, W.P. McKinley, Major William Nef Page, Samuel S. Pullman, George M. Stuart, Prof. Lewis Temple, Miss Terry, Prof. Whitman, Prof. Wilson, Walter H. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, March 9 - March 17, 1896, Armour, G.A. Blaine, Mrs. Emmons Burton Cook, Prof. A.S. Darrow, Mr. Dewey, Prof. Ferguson, R.H. Halsted, George Bruce Hewett, W.T. Hirsch, Dr. Jastrow, Morris Leiter, Joseph Mackenzie, Prof. W.D. Martin, Mrs. Franklin H. Nixon, William Penn Potter, Mrs. Mary Salisbury, Prof. Shorey Small Starr, Prof. Trude, A.S. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, March 17 - April 13, 1896, Belfield, H.K. Blaine, Mrs. Blair, H.H. Breasted, James H. Burton, E.D. Chamberlin, T.C. Cuppy, Mr. Durham, Mrs. Blanche Gunsaulus, F.W. Harper, Edward F. Harris, Pres. J.H. Haskell, Mrs. Jastrow, Prof. Kemper, J.F. Lane, Supt. of Schools Lasher, G.W. Leiter, Joseph Lovett Moses, Prof. Bernard Northrup, Mrs. Peabody, Jas. Powell, T.W. Riding, William H. Rogers, Dr. L.D. Talcott, W.A. Thomas, W.I. Young, Ella Flagg (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, April 13, - May 11, 1896, Carpenter, F.I. Chamberlin, T.C. Coulter, Prof. Dillon, Mrs. A.J. Dow, Augustus Fiske, Prof. Fuller, Sec. Gallup, Frank Haskell, Mrs. Caroline Ickes, H.L. Iddings, J.P. Ingals, Dr. E. Fletcher Kohlsaat, H.H. Luke, Mrs. R.C. Matran, Benjamin F. McClintock, W.D. McKee, W.P. Moscrip, Rev. C.H. Nash, Rev. H.C. Peck, F.W. Talbot, Miss Yerkes, Charles T. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, May 11, - May 23, 1896, Belfield, H.H. Bray, Mr. Brown, Scott Carpenter, F.G. Child, Mr. Cosmopolitan Magazine, Editor Coulter, Prof. Culver, Helen Dewing, Dr. W.H. Elliott, Francis P. Grant, Mr. Haskell, Mrs. Hughitt, Pres. CandN, R.R. Jones, Lewis H., Supt. of Schools Judson McKee McLeish, Andrew Parker, Francis W. Slater, Mr. Taintor, J.F. Talbot, Dr. Winthrop White, Rev. I.A. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, May 25 - June 30, 1896, Ames, E.S. Armour, Philip D. Bray, J.W. Breyfogle, Caroline Burrows, Mrs. H.E. Buttrick, Wallace Choate, Joseph H. Culver, Helen Ellison, Olaf Goodspeed, George S. Hammond, W.W. Harper, Samuel (father) James, Prof. Manchester, H.H. McAndrews, W.A. Porter, J.J. Shepardson, Mr. Stuart, Lewis Wallace, A.S. White, Charles D. Yerkes Zeublin (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, July 1 - August 10, 1897, Barnard, Prof. E.E. Cheney, Joseph Loring Choate, Joseph H. Faunce, W.H.P. Gage, Lyman J. Harper's father Haskell, Mrs. Heath, Mr. (by Miss Cobb) James, Mr. Kelvin, Lord Morehouse, H.L. Rand, John C. Robinson, Mrs. Harriet Salisbury Silva, C.P. and W.P. Stuart, Prof. Lewis Vincent, George (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, August 10 - September 29, 1897, Andrews, Prof. Benjamin Bailey, O.J. Barrows, Dr. Bartlett, A.C. Colwell, Prof. R.S. Coulter, Prof. Faunce, W.H.P. Fowler, Henry T. Heath, Mr. Hewitt, Dr. Paul, Rev. David Pope, Rev. E.R. Raymond, Jerome H. Ryerson Simpson, Mr. Sisson, Mr. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, September 29 - October 16, 1897, The Academic Richard Wagner Society Barrows, Dr. John Henry Cheney, Bishop Cocke, Chas. L. Fitzgerald, Mr. Grant, Mr. Hale, Prof. Jesse, Pres. R.H. Kelly, Rev. A.C. Kent, Sydney H. Kohlsaat, H.H. Leach, Prof. Abby Leach Lester, H.V. Northrup, Dr. Parker, Francis W. Raycroft, Mr. Raymond, Jerome H. Richelt, John A. Strong, Augustus H. Taft, Lorado Wayland, H.L. Williams, Wardner Yerkes, Charles T. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, October 18 - November 15, 1897, Board of Education, Sec. of Butler, James D. Caldwell, Prof. Choate, Joseph H. Donnelley, R.R. Gottheil, Prof. Richard Gunsaulus Hale, Mr. Houghteling, James L. Hughitt, Pres. Marvin International Society Kohlsaat, Judge C.C. Leach, Abby McCarthy, Mr. Middlekauff, Harriet Miller, Ethel Pardee, K.C. Rand, John C. Raymond, Jerome H. Walker, Mr. Washington, Booker T. Young, Miss (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, November 16 - December 9, 1897, Acly, Julia H.C. Birmingham, Ernest P. Bryan, George J. Butler, Nicholas Murray Cheyne, Prof. T.K. Cohn, Adolph Culver, Helen Dewing, W. H. Fairbairn, A.M. Gregory, D.S. Judson Lowden, Frank Millikan, R.A. Shimer, Mrs. F.S.W. Starrett, Mrs. Helen E. Stetson, Pres. H.L. Taylor, Pres. J.M. Tupper, Frederick (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, December 10 - December 24, 1897, Acly, Julia H.C. Bulter, Nicholas Murray Carter, Mr. Leslie Davida Dewey, Prof. Donald, F.C. Foote Crow, Mrs. Martha Harrison, Hon. Carter H. Hatfield, Dr. Henry Rand Hempl, Prof. Hillis, Dr. Ingals, Dr. E. Fletcher Kelsey, Francis W. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, December 24 - December 29, 1897, Leiter, Joseph Reed, W.W. Rhodes, Dr. Rowley, Francis H. Salisbury, Mr. Stewart, Rev. W.J. Angell, Pres. James B. Butler, Pres. Nathaniel Butler Goodspeed, George Gunsaulus Knight, Prof. William Mathews, Shailer McKenzie, Rev. Alex. Stein, Robert Talcott, W.A. Taylor, Pres. White, And. D. Whitman, Pres. B.L. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, January 5 - January 13, 1898, Arrowsmith, R. Cuppy of Press Donnelley, Thomas E. French Educational Committee, graduation address? Herrick, Robert Holland, W.J. Horswell, Prof. Charles Irwell, Lawrence Lee, Gerald Stanley Lloyd, Henry McPherson, Dr. D.J. Rainsford Sisson, E.O. Triggs, Oscar L. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, January 13 - January 24, 1898, Belfield, H.H. Crandall, L.A. Curtis, Edward L. Gilbert, Supt. Newell D. Gribi, Theo. Hutchison, J.C. Kemp, Y.M. Lowden, F.S. Massey, John E. Mcleish, Meany, Edmund S. Metcalf, John M.P. Millikan, R.A. Morton, Joy Paul, Rev. David Wilkinson, Prof. W.C. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, January 24 - January 28, 1898, Barnes, Prof. C.R. Belfield, H.H. Bridgeman, Walter R. Dewey Geddes, Prof. Patrick Hervey, Mr. Himan, Russell (of American Book Company) Lyman, Henry M. Morton, Joy Northrup, Dr. Rein, Prof. W. Ryerson Semitic Dept. Thunber, Prof. C.H. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, January 28 - February 1, 1898, Acley, Julia H.C. Crandall, C.E. Field, Phil V. Forrest, Prof. J.D. Henderson, Dr. C.R. Hobbs, Rev. E.A. Jastrow, Prof. Joseph Joslyn, Miss Mabel L. Keeler, Prof. Linscott, Henry F. McPherson, Dr. S.J. Phelps, O.S. Seavey, Harriet L. Talbot, Miss Taylor, President J.M. (of Vassar) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, February 2 - February 11, 1898, Bonet-Maury, Prof. Buck, Prof. Hale, Mr. Hill, Rev. C.M. Horswell, Charles Kohlsaat, H.H. Lincoln, Hon. Robert T. See, T.J.J. Senn, Dr. Nicholas Sprauge, Otho S.A. Triggs, Oscar L. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, February 13 - March 4, 1898, Bailey, Charlotte O. Bartlett, A.C. Bowers, Lloyd W. Flagler, Mr. Flood, Dr. T.L. Harris, Commissioner W.T. Hatcher, William E. Herrick, E.C. Horwell, Charles Hyde, Dr. James Nevins Kemper, C.J. Linkletter, L.G. Manley, J.M. McKee, W.P. Stetson, John B. Wadsworth, Mr. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, March 4 - March 15 1898, Baldwin, Jesse Bowers, Lloyd W. Bridgeman, W. R. Butts, Miss Gallup, F.A. Gordis, W.S. Houghteling, W.L. Lane, Supt. Albert G. Laughlin, J.L. McClintock Miller, Newman Nightingale, Supt. Payne, Rev. John W. Salisbury Small, Albion Stetson, Pres. Terry, Prof. Young, Otto (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, March 15 - March 31, 1898, Acley, Julia Bonet-Maury, Prof. Bradshaw, Charles Campbell, Judge J.A. Furber, Harry J. Grant, Mr. Gunsaulus, Dr. Hyde, Dr. James Nevins Ingalls, Dr. James, Prof. Lawson, Victor F. MacLaurin, Rev. Donald D. Miller, Newman Paul, Dr. Powell, Rev. W.E. Ryerson Van Osdel, Dr. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, April 4 - May 3, 1898, Armstrong, George Belfield, H.H. Bray, J.W. Capps Chamberlain, Miss Committee on Nominations of Hyde Park Sunday School Endly, J.W. Flugel, Prof. Ewald Geddes, Prof. Patrick Harrison, Hon. Carter H. Levering, Joshua MacLaurin, Donald D. Ryerson, Shepardson Talcott, W.A. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, May 4 - May 12, 1898, Clifford, Dr. Ewing, Prof. J.T. Fiske, H.S. Forbes, Pres. J.F. Hamilton, Adebert Hodges, Prof. George Hughitt, Pres. Marvin Johnson, Herrick Kellogg, President Mallory Manly, J.M. Paul, Rev. David Sampson, Lewis D. Sission, Mr. Stetson Talbot, Miss Van Osdel, Rev. O.W. White, George E. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, May 12 - May 31. 1898, Boutell, H.S. Brown, Glenn Burnham, Prof. Ewing, Mrs. Emma Faunce, Mr. Haskell, Mrs. Caroline Heath, D.C. Kellogg, Pres. Martin Leonard, Gardner C. Mann, Hon. James R. Mead, Mr. Pearce, H.J. Purinton, President Sampson, Lewis D. Sission Smith, Mr. Stetson Thompson, S.H. Walker, George C. Walton, Mathew Whitman, Mr. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, May 31 - June 23, 1898, Acly, Miss Andrews, Pres. E.B. (missing) Bulkley, Julia Butler Buzzell, Mr. Dabney, Charles W. Fallows, Dr. Gage, Lyman J. Harper, Davida Herrick, Robert Mitchell, John J. Moore, E.H. Neumann, Dr. Theodor Runyon, William H. Scribner, Charles Sellon, L.J. Stone, Miss M.L. Stott, Pres. W.T. Thurber, Mr. Zeublen (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, June 23 - July 9, 1898, Goldman, Jennie Goldsmith, I. Hall, Charles Cuthbert Harrison, Mayor Carter H. Haskell, Mrs. Jesse, President Jones, Miss Nightingale, Mr. Simpson, Mrs. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, July 6 - July 21, 1898, Bartlett, A.C. Boyd, Mr. Bruce, Miss Chandler, F.R. Furber, Harry J. Hale, G.E. Hall, Charles Cuthbert Harper, Davida Harper, Samuel (father) Harris, Edward L. Haskell, Mrs. Hoyt, John W. Hulbert, E.B. Hurd, Dr. C.A. Mabie, Hamilton Wright MacClintock, Mr. Secretary of the Interior Walker, G.C. Waterman, Richard Wilson, William L. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, July 22 - August 4, 1898, Anderson, Rev. F.L. Andrews, Pres. Benjamin Bonet-Maury, G. Capps Hale, G.E. Ingals, Dr. Ishkubb, G. Jokisch, H.J. Mathews, S. Miller, Lewis Nightingale, Supt. Rabb, Robert M. Skinner, Mr. Stagg Starr, F. Stephenson, Thomas Terry Vincent. G.E. Wadsworth Walling, Willoughby Young, Otto (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, August 4 - September 1, 1898, Andrews, Supt. E. Benjamin Bumstead, Arthur Cobb, Miss Coles, Robert Coulter, John G. Culver, Miss Davis, Prof. N.K.Hale, G.E. Dewey, Mr.Judson Fish, Frederick S. Goodspeed, Edgar J. Gray, Mrs. Hale, G.E. James, Mr. Jones, Miss Kohlsaat, C.C. Palmer, Lieut. John M. Ryerson Selfridge, H.G. Shorey Smith, Byron L. Truax, Mr. Van Slyke, Mrs. W.M. Wallace, Elizabeth (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, September 2 - September 14, 1898, Abbott Bitting, W.C. Chase, Wayland J. Conger, Charles T. Cutting, Prof. S.V. Dickerson, J.S. Flood, Mr. Hancock, Mr. Harris, Pres. Graham Harrison, Hon. Benjamin Mabie, Rev. Henry C. Mathews Parker, Elizabeth J. Rogers, Pres. Henry Wade Ryerson Seidenadel, Dr. Senn, Dr. Nicholas Smith, Albert L. Taylor, Graham (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, September 14 - 23, 1898, Anderson, Frederick Abbott, Prof. Adams, Pres. C.K. Blaine, Mrs. Emmons Dawes, Hon. C.M. Hall, G. Stanley Henderson, C.R. Hillis, Newell Dwight Kohlsaat, H.H. Lawrence, William M. Miller, Charles Secretary of State Williston, C.S. Young, Otto (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, September 24 - October 18, 1898, Abernethy, Alonzo Angell, President Bowne, Prof. Borden Core, A.S. Coulter Donaldson, H.H. French, C.W. Freund, Dr. Gage, Lyman J. Graduate School Facutly Hall, Charles Cuthbert Hall, G. Stanley Hektoen, Dr. L. Judson Keen, W.W. Parker, A.K. Robinson, Willard H. Searles, H. Clay Starr Von Holst, Mrs. Wilson, S.A. unidentified (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, October 22 - November 3, 1898, Blaine, Mrs. Emmons Cavanaugh, Mr. Commercial Advertiser, Editor of Fisher, Dr. Geo. P. Holbrook, P.K. Judson Keeler, W.P. Miller, F.J. Norlin, George Palmer, Mrs. Potter Parker, Dr. A.K. Porter, J.A. Price, L.T.C. Raymond, Jerome H. Salisbury Sellon, L.J. Small Smith, George Adam Taylor, Pres. I.M. Vincent, Mrs. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, November 4 - 30, 1898, Blake, E. Nelson Day, W.M. Denton, H.A. Dickerson, J.S. Douglass, W.H. Driver, S. R. Ettinger, C.N. Hale, G.E. Harris, N.W. Henrotin, Mrs. Ellen M. Hoyt, John W. James Lanman, Col. Geo. V. Lawson, Victor Loeb, Assoc. Prof. Magdalene Soceity, President of the Miller, Robert A. Newcomb, Prof. Simon Rabe, Otto A. Rand, E.K. Talbot, Miss Wilson, Walter H. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, November 30 - December 20, 1898, Andrews, Supt. (missing) Angell, James B. Bitting, W.C. Bowen, C.C. Coulter Dodgson, Mr. Driver, Prof. S.R. Herrick, Pres. C.L. Lewis, E.H. McDonald, E.H. McKinley, President William McPherson, Dr. Nickell, A.H. Parker, F.W. Talbot, Miss Thurber, C.H. Vosburgh, Geo. B. Wallace, James F. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, December 20 - December 31, 1898, Brainerd, Harriet C. Canfield, Pres. James. H. Chandler, Prof. Chase, Wayland J. Ellis, Mrs. A.M.M. French, W.M.R. Hale, W.G. Hallinan, Charles T. Hulbert, Dr. E.B. Johnson, Rossiter Laves, Dr. Mamie McLeish, Bruce Ream, Norman B. Schurz, Hon. Carl Talcott, W. A. Votaw, Clyde H. Wilkinson, Prof. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, January 3 - January 12, 1899, Atwood, Wallace N. Barrows, Rev. J.H. Bulkley, Miss Burton, E. D. Dewey Flagg, R. C. Goodspeed, George Moulton, Prof. Reinstein, J.B. Salisbury Slocum, Pres. Stewart, W.J. Terry Wallace, John F. Young, Mr. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, January 16 - January 24, 1899, Bulkley, Miss Chamberlain, T.C. Editor of Elkhorn, Wis. Republican Felsenthal, E.D. Fisher, Albert Judson Freund Heath, D.C. Johnson, Rossiter (Appleton) Lewis, Mary Louise Lovett, William P. McCormick, Harold F. McLeish, A. Michelson Mitchell, A.C. Reinstein, J.B. Salisbury Small Talbot, Miss Walker, John B. Wheaton, Archibald Wilkinson, W.C. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, January 24 - February 8, 1899, Beach, H.H. Blaine, Mrs. Emmons Colwell, Prof. Donaldson, H.H. Garlick, Wynn N. Gilmore, George W. Hale, W.C. Hastings, Wm. W. Hathaway, Prof. A.S. Haynes, Rev. M.W. Hyde, Mr. Moore, E.H. Payne, John W. Porter, J.A. Shepardson, F.W. Stratton Stuart, Prof. Lewis Tufts Young, Miss Ella (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, February 8 - 21, 1899, Bartlett, Miss Emiline B. Bonet-Maury Braithwaite, Edward E. Bumpus, H.C. Capps Coulter Foote Crow, Martha Graduate School Faculty Jordan, Pres. David S. Kinney, Mrs. C.S. Nolan, J.H. Roosevelt, Theodore Ryerson Schwill, Ferdinand Seymour, R.G. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, February 21, 1899 - March 23, 1899, Adams, Pres. C.K. Budde, Prof. K. Butler, Edward B. Dewey Donaldson, H. H. Donnelley Foster, Miss Harper, Davida Lyman, Dr. McCartney, W. S. Moore, E.H. Rogers, Dr. Henry Wade Rogers, H.H. Ryerson Scott, Colin A. Smith, Franklyn C. Sprague, O.S.A. Taylor, A. M. (Pres, Vassar) Welch, Lewis S. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, April 3 - 8, 1899, Blaine, Mrs. Bridge, Dr. Norman Buttrick, Wallace Capps, Mrs. Davis, Dr. Edward P. Dewey, John Faunce, Rev. W.H.P. Field, Rev. J.N. Gross, S.E. Kellogg, Pres. James H. Mathews, Shailer Moore, Carrie S. Reinstein, Mr. Seaton, Mrs. Florence Shutts, H.J. Sprague, O.S.A. Stetson, H.L. Von Holst (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, April 8 - 27, 1899, Billings, C.J.G. Brown, D.E. Coulter Dickerson, Mrs. Emma R. Donaldson Hale, Mr. Haskell, Mrs. Howerth, Mr. Lengeld, Mr. Leonard, Gardner C. Mall, Dr. Franklin P. McKee, Dean W.P. Rayl, R.A. Ryerson Seaton, Mrs. Florence P. Smily, Wm. H. Van Dyke, Henry Wallace, Miss (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, April 29 - May 8, 1899, Arnold, Joseph K. Brophy, Dr. Cooke, Majorie Crew, Miss Caroline Ladd Davis, Mr. Ellsworth, P. A. Faunce, Dr. Gentles, Dr. Grosscup, Judge Peter S. Kent, Sydney Linzee, C.F. Linzer, C.F. McKee, W. P. Rabb, Robert M. Rayl, R.A. Raymond, Pres. J.H. Reinstein Smith, George Adam Stratton (Box 4, Folder 27)